http://www.pricecutter.com/privacy

Router Bits, Woodworking Supplies, Woodworking Tools - EagleAmerica.com
COVID-19 Notice: Please e-mail
eagle@eagleamerica.com for help and support. Phone operators can process orders only. (
More Info)
Continue Shopping
Checkout »
PowerLift PRO
Revolutionary Routing.
Rocky 30 Router
High performance, small size.
Save $15 with Value Package
Phenolic Router Table
Strong and Stable.
OLSON All Pro Blades
Premium Quality. Long Life.
Universal Mounting System
SALE! SAVE $40!
Doweling Jig
Self-Centering
SALE! SAVE $15!
Plug & Tenon Cutter Set
No-Slip Hex Shanks
SALE! SAVE $23!
Perfect Sanding Anywhere
NEW! SAVE $50!
HVLP Sprayer
Paint Anything Like a Pro
NEW!
Spindle & Belt Sander
2 Tools in One
NEW Video!
Preserve Wood Oils
Beautifies and Protects
Buy More, Save More SALE!
/privacy
Privacy Policy
Eagle America respects your privacy and the security of your personal information. For this reason, we have updated our Privacy Policy (“Policy”) as of May 25, 2018. It describes how Eagle America Industries (“Eagle America”, “we”, “our”, or “us”) collects, uses and shares personal information when you access our website, contact us by phone, email, and chat or connect with us in any other manner, including in our social media channels. We periodically update this Privacy Policy and reserve the right to change the provisions of this Policy or our privacy practices at any time.
Your Consent
By providing personal information and/or non-personal information to us through the Site or through our customer service department in connection with our Site or Catalog, you are agreeing to let Eagle America collect and use your information as described in the Privacy Policy.
What is personal information?
"Personal information" means information that specifically identifies an individual person, such as name, mailing address, email address, phone number, or account number. It may also include other information about you, such as gender, date of birth, or other demographic information, or about your use of the Site, such as IP address or cookies, if that other information is linked to your personal information.
Collection of Your Information
Information you Provide to Us
Eagle America collects personal information that you provide to us. We may collect information (including name, billing and shipping address, telephone number, email address, transaction information and credit card information) when you:
Place an order over the phone from our catalogs or on our website
Add yourself to a product’s wait list on our website
Return an item or make an exchange
Request a catalog
Create an account at eagleamerica.com or checkout as a guest
Sign up for Eagle America emails
Are referred to us through a marketing promotion
Provide a product review on our website
Otherwise submitting personal information to us
Information from Other Sources
We also may collect information about you from third party sources. The information we collect from third party sources may include things like demographic information and purchase preference information. The third party sources may include public databases‚ social media platforms‚ data append services‚ data sharing cooperatives‚ and others.
Automated Information Collection
We also collect some of your information automatically when you visit this Site. For example, this Site collects your IP address, Internet Service Provider (ISP), login information, operating system, clickstream data and other online identifiers and records the pages that you visit and other information about your activity on the Site (e.g. Information you enter during the checkout process).
Like many other websites, we may use “cookies”, pixels/web beacons and other technologies to receive and store certain types of information. This information helps us customize your website experience and make our marketing messages more relevant, improve customer online shopping experience, help with fraud identification and to assist our customer service representatives in resolving issues customers may experience in completing online purchases. In order to provide the best customer experience possible, we also use this information for reporting and analysis purposes, such as how you are shopping our website, performance of our marketing efforts, and your response to those marketing efforts. If you reject cookies, you may still use our Site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our Site may be limited. We may also work with third-parties providers who may use cookies on our Site. You can block cookies by activating the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. For more information about cookies, including how to set your internet browser to reject cookies, please go to www.allaboutcookies.org or www.networkadvertising.org.
Single Sign-On Services
We may also use single sign-on services that allow you to sign into this Site using your third-party social networking login credentials for accounts such as Facebook. This allows you to link your existing social network profile to your Site account. Once connected‚ you will be able to post content on the third-party website from this Site and interact with your friends from the third-party site(s). Any information or content that you post to the third-party website will be subject to that website’s own privacy policy. We may also access and use available information from your third-party social network profile‚ such as your name‚ location‚ profile picture and information‚ gender‚ list of friends‚ friends’ profiles or postings‚ email address‚ wall postings and news feed.
What we do with your information
At Eagle America we want to provide you with a great shopping experience and fulfill your orders in an efficient manner. To do this, we may collect and use your personal information to:
Process and track your order
Send you an order and shipping confirmation email
Product returns
Provide the services you request
Contact you about the status of an order
Send you catalogs or promotional offers we believe will be of interest to you
Send requested product or service information
Send you Eagle America email updates (e.g., coupons) or otherwise respond to questions, concerns, and customer support inquiries.
To administer surveys‚ sweepstakes‚ contests‚ and promotions
Identify your product and service preferences
Customize our communications to you
Improve our merchandise selection and customer service
Improve the effectiveness of the Site, mobile experience, and marketing efforts
Conduct research and analysis, including surveys.
Prevent fraudulent transactions, monitor against theft and otherwise protect our customers and our business
Information We Share with Others and Your Privacy Rights
We contract with other companies to provide certain services, including shipping, name and address verification, email distribution, market research, third party advertising and payment processing (to view PayPal's privacy policy, please visit https://www.paypal.com/privacy). We provide these companies with only the information they need to perform their services and work closely with them to ensure that your privacy is respected and protected. These companies are prohibited by contract from using this information for their own marketing purposes or from sharing this information with anyone other than Eagle America.
Marketing Purposes: From time to time, we make our mailing list (names and addresses only) available to other reputable organizations whose products or services we believe will be of interest to you. We do not share email addresses for this purpose.
Legal Requirements‚ Safety‚ and Loss Prevention: We may disclose your personal information in other special circumstances. For example, we may provide personal information about you to regulatory authorities and law enforcement officials in accordance with applicable law‚ when we otherwise believe in good faith that the law requires it‚ or to respond to requests from government authorities. There may be instances when we may use or disclose your personal information in order to protect or defend the legal rights‚ property or operations of Lands’ End or our employees or agents; to protect the rights‚ privacy‚ safety or security of users‚ members or others; to protect against fraud; and to allow us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain. We do not provide information to these agencies or companies for marketing or commercial purposes.
Your Rights to Access and Control your Data
You have many choices about how your data is collected, used and shared.
If you would like to opt out of Eagle America promotional emails or receive fewer emails‚ please follow the unsubscribe link at the bottom of each such email or contact us at https://www.eagleamerica.com/contact.
If you do not want to receive mailings from other reputable companies and prefer that we do not share any information with these companies, please Contact Us.
If you would like to opt out of receiving Eagle America catalogs‚ please contact us at one of the channels listed in the Contact Us section of our Site.
So that we can be sure to identify you correctly, please provide us with your full name‚ the types of communications you would like to receive or not receive‚ and your contact information. For example, if you would like to opt-out of receiving catalogs‚ make sure to include your mailing address in your communication to us. Because catalog mailings and promotional emails are planned in advance, please allow a reasonable time for your preferences to be processed. It may take up to 10 days to process your requests related to email. Please note that requested changes to the Mailing List may take up to eight (8) weeks to take effect, particularly if we are removing your name from our postal mailings.
We may still contact you for transactional purposes such as customer service‚ product information‚ and more. We may also contact you with questions or information regarding your order‚ such as regarding order status‚ shipment‚ or refunds.
To opt-out of direct personalized advertising on the Internet from Eagle America, click here. If you choose to opt-out of direct personalized advertising, you may still see advertisements on the internet from Eagle America, however, such advertisements were not generated by use of your personal information.
We may retain your personal data even after you have made certain choices if reasonably necessary to comply with our legal obligations (including law enforcement requests), meet regulatory requirements, resolve disputes, maintain security, prevent fraud and abuse, or fulfill your request to "unsubscribe" from further messages from us. We also may also retain de-personalized information after honoring your request(s).
For E.U. Residents Only: If you are a resident of the European Union and you would like to take advantage of any of your rights under the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), such as your Right to Erasure (otherwise known as the “Right to be Forgotten”) please contact Eagle America customer service department and we will be happy to assist you.
How Eagle America Protects Personal Information
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online and that resides in our internal network. We use these procedures to better safeguard your information. We also take reasonable steps to ensure that third parties who work with us to make the Site (including the software, applications and services provided on the Site) available to you agree to protect personal information that they must access in order to serve you and to honor your preferences about contacts you receive. However, Eagle America shall have no liability or responsibility for the privacy practices or other actions of any third-party service provider or any other third-party site or service that may be enabled within the Service.
When you send or otherwise transmit your sensitive information (such as your credit card number) to or though the Site, your sensitive information is encrypted and protected with SSL, the current industry-standard encryption protocol. One way to check to see if you are on a secure page is to check the URL or address of the page. (Look in the address box or right-click on the page and select "Properties".) These secure SSL-encrypted pages have URLs that start with "https://" instead of "http://".
Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as required and only authorized individuals are permitted access to the information that you provide to us. We take physical, technical and administrative measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of Personal Information, however; we cannot guarantee that these measures will prevent breaches of the integrity and security of our network and systems, or that Personal Information will never be accessed or acquired by unauthorized persons, notwithstanding the safeguards we have in place. Without limiting the terms of this Privacy Policy, you understand that we do not guarantee that your use of the Site and/or information provided by you will be private or secure and we are not responsible or liable to you for any lack of privacy or security you may experience. You are fully responsible for taking precautions and providing security measures best suited for your situation and intended use of the Site. You also understand that any information provided by you or collected by us or our agents in connection with your use of the Site will be used in the manner described in our Terms of Use. Please do not use the Site if you do not agree to the terms and conditions described in this section.
Privacy of Children
Protecting the rights of children is very important to Eagle America. Our website is not intended for use by children under the age of 13 and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 18, you may only use eagleamerica.com with the help of a parent or guardian.
Additional Security and How to Protect YourSELF
We also ask customers to carefully review their accounts and immediately report any unexpected activity to us and their issuing bank or credit card company. We ask all our customers to take measures to help protect information in their online accounts, including the following:
Install the latest security updates and anti-virus software on your computer to help prevent malware and viruses.
Reset your e-mail account passwords frequently.
Use complex passwords or passphrases
Do not use the same password on more than one website.
Do not share your password with others.
Sign out/log off website sessions so that your session is closed and cannot be accessed by another user on the same computer, especially when using a public computer or terminal.
Email Security: Please note that e-mail may not be encrypted and is not considered to be a secure means of transmitting credit card information. “Phishing” is a scam designed to steal your information. If you receive an e-mail that looks like it is from us asking you for certain information, do not respond. Though we might ask you your name, we will never request your password, credit card information or other information through e-mail.
Visitors from Outside of the United States
The Service is hosted in the United States. If you are visiting the Service from outside the United States, your information may be transferred to, stored and processed in the United States in accordance with this Privacy Policy and applicable US laws. Please note that data protection and other applicable laws of the United States may not be as comprehensive as those laws or regulations in your country or may otherwise differ from the data protection or consumer protection laws in your country. By using the Service, you consent to transfer of your information to our facilities as described in this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions about security of the Site, please contact us.
We may disclose your personal information
As required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process;
When we believe, in good faith, that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, enforce our terms and conditions, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request;
If Eagle America is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets; and
To any other third party, with your prior consent to do so.
You may review, update, or modify your online account information, including profile and contact information, at any time by logging into your Eagle America online account. You may permanently delete your Eagle America Accounts by contacting us here.
Contact Us
For questions or comments related to your privacy, we invite you to contact our customer service department. We’re always here to help.
For other types of comments, questions, or for assistance placing an order, please visit our website at eagleamerica.com or call us directly at 1-800-872-2511.
Follow Us
Sign up for our eNewsletter
Quicklinks
Member Account
FAQs
Gift Cards/Gift Certificates
Order Tracking
Find a Wishlist
© Copyright 2020 Eagle America. All Rights Reserved.
×
This site uses cookies to collect data. By continuing to browse, you accept our Privacy Policy. Agree
